<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
    <popular>
        <description>Games that everyone is talking about...</description>
        <game id="1">
            <title>The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time</title>
            <short_description>As a young boy, Link is tricked by Ganondorf, the King of the Gerudo Thieves.</short_description>
            <full_description>Join Link on an epic quest to save Hyrule from the evil Ganondorf.</full_description>
            <release_date>NOV 23, 1998</release_date>
            <rating>E</rating>
            <author>Nintendo</author>
            <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uHGShqcAHlQ/maxresdefault.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="2">
            <title>SoulCalibur</title>
            <short_description>This is a tale of souls and swords, transcending the world and all its history, told for all eternity...</short_description>
            <full_description>The greatest weapons-based fighter returns, this time on Sega Dreamcast. Soul Calibur unleashes incredible graphics, fantastic fighters, and combos so amazing they'll make your head spin!</full_description>
            <release_date>SEP 8, 1999</release_date>
            <rating>T</rating>
            <author>Project Soul</author>
            <publisher>Namco</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://www.metacritic.com/a/img/catalog/provider/6/3/6-1-7379-13.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="3">
            <title>Grand Theft Auto IV</title>
            <short_description>[Metacritic's 2008 Xbox 360 Game of the Year; Also known as "GTA IV"]</short_description>
            <full_description>Experience the story of Niko Bellic as he navigates the criminal underworld of Liberty City.</full_description>
            <release_date>APR 29, 2008</release_date>
            <rating>M</rating>
            <author>Rockstar North</author>
            <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/vi/b/b7/Grand_Theft_Auto_IV_cover.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="4">
            <title>Super Mario Galaxy</title>
            <short_description>2007 Wii Game of the Year. The ultimate Nintendo hero is taking the ultimate step ... out into space.</short_description>
            <full_description>Join Mario as he explores the galaxy to rescue Princess Peach from Bowser's clutches.</full_description>
            <release_date>NOV 12, 2007</release_date>
            <rating>E</rating>
            <author>Nintendo</author>
            <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/7/76/SuperMarioGalaxy.jpg/220px-SuperMarioGalaxy.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="5">
            <title>Super Mario Galaxy 2</title>
            <short_description>Super Mario Galaxy 2, the sequel to the galaxy-hopping original game, includes the gravity-defying, physics-based exploration from the first game, but is loaded with entirely new galaxies and features to challenge players.</short_description>
            <full_description>Continue the space-faring adventure with Mario in all-new galaxies and challenges.</full_description>
            <release_date>MAY 23, 2010</release_date>
            <rating>E</rating>
            <author>Nintendo</author>
            <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/6/65/Super_Mario_Galaxy_2_Box_Art.jpg/220px-Super_Mario_Galaxy_2_Box_Art.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="6">
            <title>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild</title>
            <short_description>Ignore everything you know about The Legend of Zelda games.</short_description>
            <full_description>Embark on a breathtaking open-world adventure as Link and discover the secrets of Hyrule.</full_description>
            <release_date>MAR 3, 2017</release_date>
            <rating>E10+</rating>
            <author>Nintendo</author>
            <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/vi/thumb/c/c6/The_Legend_of_Zelda_Breath_of_the_Wild.jpg/220px-The_Legend_of_Zelda_Breath_of_the_Wild.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="7">
            <title>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</title>
            <short_description>Challenge up to four friends in online competitions over a LAN or the Internet. Take them on in both Trick Attack and Graffiti modes.</short_description>
            <full_description>Experience the thrill of skateboarding with Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3, featuring online multiplayer and iconic skate spots.</full_description>
            <release_date>OCT 30, 2001</release_date>
            <rating>T</rating>
            <author>Neversoft</author>
            <publisher>Activision</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/2/2b/Tony_Hawk%27s_Pro_Skater_3_Coverart.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="8">
            <title>Perfect Dark (2000)</title>
            <short_description>Step into the Dark... As Carrington Institute's most promising new Agent, Joanna Dark must uncover the truth behind the dataDyne Corporation's recent technological breakthroughs - breakthroughs which could have serious consequences for mankind.</short_description>
            <full_description>Join Joanna Dark in a thrilling first-person shooter as she uncovers a conspiracy that could threaten the world.</full_description>
            <release_date>MAY 22, 2000</release_date>
            <rating>M</rating>
            <author>Rare</author>
            <publisher>Rare</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://www.gamespot.com/a/uploads/scale_medium/mig/0/2/1/1/2210211-198274_27981_front.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="9">
            <title>Red Dead Redemption 2</title>
            <short_description>Developed by the creators of Grand Theft Auto V and Red Dead Redemption, Red Dead Redemption 2 is an epic tale of life in America’s unforgiving heartland.</short_description>
            <full_description>Experience an epic tale of life in America's unforgiving heartland in Red Dead Redemption 2.</full_description>
            <release_date>OCT 26, 2018</release_date>
            <rating>M</rating>
            <author>Rockstar Games</author>
            <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a7/Red_Dead_Redemption.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="10">
            <title>Grand Theft Auto V</title>
            <short_description>The sprawling sun-soaked metropolis of Los Santos is chock full of self-help coaches, starlets and C-List celebrities, once on top of the media world, now struggling to stay relevant in time of economic malaise and lowest-common-denominator reality TV.</short_description>
            <full_description>Explore the sun-soaked metropolis of Los Santos in the critically acclaimed open-world game Grand Theft Auto V.</full_description>
            <release_date>NOV 18, 2014</release_date>
            <rating>M</rating>
            <author>Rockstar North</author>
            <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a5/Grand_Theft_Auto_V.png</image>
        </game>
        <game id="11">
            <title>Metroid Prime</title>
            <short_description>Samus returns in a new mission to unravel the mystery behind the ruined walls scattered across Tallon IV.</short_description>
            <full_description>Join Samus Aran in Metroid Prime as she explores the mysterious planet Tallon IV and uncovers its secrets.</full_description>
            <release_date>NOV 17, 2002</release_date>
            <rating>T</rating>
            <author>Retro Studios</author>
            <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/b/ba/MetroidPrimebox.jpg/220px-MetroidPrimebox.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="12">
            <title>Grand Theft Auto III</title>
            <short_description>Players are put at the heart of their very own gangster movie, and let loose in a fully-realised 3 dimensional city with a cast of hundreds, 50 plus vehicles, ranging from sports cars to ice cream trucks and from boats to buses, 3 hours of music, including opera, reggae, house, drum and bass, pop and disco, and a huge array of street ready weapons.</short_description>
            <full_description>Experience the groundbreaking open-world gameplay of Grand Theft Auto III and explore Liberty City.</full_description>
            <release_date>OCT 22, 2001</release_date>
            <rating>M</rating>
            <author>DMA Design</author>
            <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/vi/thumb/b/be/GTA3boxcover.jpg/220px-GTA3boxcover.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="13">
            <title>Super Mario Odyssey</title>
            <short_description>New Evolution of Mario Sandbox-Style Gameplay. Mario embarks on a new journey through unknown worlds, running and jumping through huge 3D worlds in the first sandbox-style Mario game since Super Mario 64 and Super Mario Sunshine. Set sail between expansive worlds aboard an airship, and perform all-new actions, such as throwing Mario's cap.</short_description>
            <full_description>Embark on a globe-trotting adventure with Mario in Super Mario Odyssey and discover new worlds and abilities.</full_description>
            <release_date>OCT 27, 2017</release_date>
            <rating>E10+</rating>
            <author>Nintendo</author>
            <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/8/8d/Super_Mario_Odyssey.jpg/220px-Super_Mario_Odyssey.jpg</image>
        </game>
        <game id="14">
            <title>Halo: Combat Evolved</title>
            <short_description>In a desperate attempt to keep a conquering alien race called the Covenant from finding Earth, you--a cybernetically enhanced soldier representing the peak of human military evolution--and a ragtag group of Marines flee to a distant uncharted system where you unexpectedly stumble across Halo, an enormous alien artifact in orbit between a gas giant and its moon. Your objective: Uncover Halo's horrible secret, and destroy mankind's nemesis - the Covenant.</short_description>
            <full_description>Join the fight against the Covenant in Halo: Combat Evolved and uncover the mysteries of the Halo ring.</full_description>
            <release_date>NOV 15, 2001</release_date>
            <rating>M</rating>
            <author>Bungie</author>
            <publisher>Microsoft Game Studios</publisher>
            <price>Unknown</price>
            <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/vi/thumb/b/b2/Halo_Combat_Evolved_DVD_cover.jpg/220px-Halo_Combat_Evolved_DVD_cover.jpg</image>
        </game>
    </popular>
</data>